[
    {
      "question": " Which type of JavaScript language is ___?",
  
      "option1": " Object-Oriented",
  
      "option2": " Object-Based",
  
      "option3": " Assembly-language",
  
      "option4": " High-level",
  
      "answer": " Object-Based"
},
    {
        "question": " hich one of the following also known as Conditional Expression:",
    
        "option1": " Alternative to if-else",
    
        "option2": "  Switch statement",
    
        "option3": " If-then-else statement",
    
        "option4": " immediate if",
    
        "answer": " immediate if"
      },
      {
        "question": " In JavaScript, what is a block of statement ?",
    
        "option1": " Conditional block",
    
        "option2": " block that combines a number of statements into a single compound statement",
    
        "option3": " both conditional block and a single statement",
    
        "option4": " block that contains a single statement",
    
        "answer": " block that combines a number of statements into a single compound statement"
      },
      {
        "question": " When interpreter encounters an empty statements, what it will do:",
    
        "option1": " Shows a warning",
    
        "option2": " Prompts to complete the statement",
    
        "option3": " Throws an error",
    
        "option4": " Ignores the statements",
    
        "answer": " Ignores the statements"
      },
      {
        "question": " The 'function' and 'var' are known as:",
    
        "option1": " Keywords",
    
        "option2": " Data types",
    
        "option3": " Declaration statements",
    
        "option4": " Prototypes",
    
        "answer": " Declaration statements"
      },
      {
        "question": " Which of the following variables takes precedence over the others if the names are the same ?",
    
        "option1": " Global variable",
    
        "option2": " The local element",
    
        "option3": "The two of the above",
    
        "option4": " None of the above",
    
        "answer": " The local element"
      },
      {
        "question": " Which one of the following is the correct way for calling the JavaScript code ?",
    
        "option1": " Preprocessor",
    
        "option2": " Triggering Event",
    
        "option3": " RMI",
    
        "option4": " Function/Method",
    
        "answer": " Function/Method"
      },
      {
        "question": " Which of the following type of a variable is volatile ?",
    
        "option1": " Mutable variable",
    
        "option2": " Dynamic variable",
    
        "option3": " Volatile variable",
    
        "option4": " Immutable variable",
    
        "answer": " Mutable variable"
      },
      {
        "question": " Which of the following option is used as hexadecimal literal beginning ?",
    
        "option1": " 00",
    
        "option2": " 0x",
    
        "option3": " 0X",
    
        "option4": " Both 0x and 0X",
    
        "answer": " Both 0x and 0X"
      },
      {
        "question": "When there is an indefinite or an infinite value during an arithmetic computation in a program, then JavaScript prints______.",
    
        "option1": " Prints an exception error",
    
        "option2": " Prints an overflow error",
    
        "option3": " Displays 'Infinity'",
    
        "option4": " Prints the value as such",
    
        "answer": " Displays 'Infinity'"
      }
    
    
    
]